export const data = [
  {
    category: 'general',
    created_at: '20/06/2019 04:53',
    instructor: 'elshafeay',
    mcqs: [
      {
        answer: '1',
        choice_a:
          'My friend says I can’t help you because I have a lot of work to do.',
        choice_b:
          'My friend says he can’t help me because he has a lot of work to do.',
        choice_c:
          'My friend says he can’t help me because he have a lot of work to do.',
        choice_d:
          'My friend says that I can’t help you I have a lot of work to do.',
        choice_e: null,
        exam: 'English Exam',
        id: 1,
        question:
          'My friend says, “I can’t help you, sorry. I have a lot of work to do.”',
      },
      {
        answer: '2',
        choice_a: 'My friend told me that I will meet you tonight.',
        choice_b: 'My friend told that he will meet me tonight.',
        choice_c: 'My friend told me that he would meet me that night.',
        choice_d: 'My friend said to me that he will meet me that night.',
        choice_e: null,
        exam: 'English Exam',
        id: 2,
        question: 'My friend said to me,” I will meet you tonight.”',
      },
      {
        answer: '0',
        choice_a: 'She said that she had visited Peshawar the previous day.',
        choice_b: 'She said that I had visited Peshawar yesterday.',
        choice_c: 'She said that she visited Peshawar yesterday.',
        choice_d: 'She said that she has visited Peshawar the previous day.',
        choice_e: null,

        exam: 'English Exam',
        id: 3,
        question: 'She said,” I visited Peshawar yesterday.”',
      },
      {
        answer: '2',
        choice_a: 'Hard Punishment',
        choice_b: 'Beating Someone',
        choice_c: 'Warning or Small Punishment',
        choice_d: 'Make someone sad',
        choice_e: null,

        exam: 'English Exam',
        id: 4,
        question: 'Idiom “A slap on the wrist” means?',
      },
      {
        answer: '1',
        choice_a: 'WITH',
        choice_b: 'IN',
        choice_c: 'FOR',
        choice_d: 'ON',
        choice_e: null,

        exam: 'English Exam',
        id: 5,
        question: 'He writes ___ ink.',
      },
      {
        answer: '2',
        choice_a: 'He said that I need some money.',
        choice_b: 'He said that he need some money.',
        choice_c: 'He said that he needed some money.',
        choice_d: 'He said that I needed some money.',
        choice_e: null,

        exam: 'English Exam',
        id: 6,
        question: 'He said,”I need some money.”',
      },
    ],
    subject: 'English Exam',
    pk: 1,
  },
  {
    category: 'programming',
    created_at: '20/06/2019 05:14',
    instructor: 'elshafeay',
    mcqs: [
      {
        answer: '0',
        choice_a: 'assembler',
        choice_b: 'attempter',
        choice_c: 'compiler',
        choice_d: 'debugger',
        choice_e: null,
        exam: 'Introduction to programming',
        id: 0,
        question:
          'Translator which is used to convert codes of assembly language into machine language is termed as ___',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Diagram which shows relationship between classes is termed as ___',
        id: 1,
        choice_a: 'Class diagram',
        choice_b: 'sequential diagram',
        choice_c: 'use case diagram',
        choice_e: null,
        answer: '0',
        exam: 'Introduction to programming',
      },
      {
        answer: '0',
        choice_a: 'structural language',
        choice_b: 'object oriented programming',
        choice_c: 'JAVA',
        choice_d: 'C++',
        choice_e: null,
        exam: 'Introduction to programming',
        id: 2,
        question: 'Higher-order functions are not built into the',
      },
      {
        answer: '1',
        choice_a: 'PHP',
        choice_b: 'Java script',
        choice_c: 'Visual Basic',
        choice_d: 'Visual C#',
        choice_e: null,
        exam: 'Introduction to programming',
        id: 3,
        question:
          'Animations and interactivity with user on web pages can be done by',
      },
      {
        answer: '3',
        choice_a: 'object diagram',
        choice_b: 'sequential diagram',
        choice_c: 'use case diagram',
        choice_d: 'communication diagram',
        choice_e: null,

        exam: 'Introduction to programming',
        id: 4,
        question:
          'Diagram which shows how objects communicate with each other regarding a sequence of messages is called',
      },
      {
        answer: '0',
        choice_a: 'Java',
        choice_b: 'Basic',
        choice_c: 'Pascal',
        choice_d: 'Ada',
        choice_e: null,
        exam: 'Introduction to programming',
        id: 5,
        question:
          "Programming language which sometimes called 'write once, run any where is",
      },
    ],
    pk: 2,
    subject: 'Introduction to programming',
  },
]
